<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Aboutmes on Welcome </title>
      <generator uri="https://hugo.spf13.com">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://dxrodri.github.io/www/aboutme/index.xml/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <updated>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://dxrodri.github.io/www/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dxrodri.github.io/www/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a data analytics engineer by profession based out of Chicago area. My primary interest lies in applying data analytics technologies such as big data and machine learning to financial and banking data to gain business insights and competitive advantage. With over 15 years of extensive software development expertise, I have successfully developed and managed enterprise level projects across multiple industries that includes finance, banking, logistics and telecommunications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a life long learner and have recently completed Data Science Specialization course from John Hopkins University to develop skills in the fast growing field of data analytics. In 2013, I successfully earned coveted Chartered Financial Analyst(CFA) designation after passing all three exams over a period of 4 years.  In 2009, I succesfully passed FINRA&amp;rsquo;s Series 3 exam. Over the years I have completed multiple technical certifications including Java, Service Oriented Architecture and Object Oriented Analysis and Design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of my personal projects in the field of data analytics are published at:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=https://dxrodri.shinyapps.io/shinyapps/ class=not-printed&gt;Data Science Projects Using R and Shiny&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=https://public.tableau.com/profile/domr#!/ class=not-printed&gt;Data Visualization Projects Using Tableau Public&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can be reached via email &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:dxrodri at gmail.com&#34;&gt;dxrodri at gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; or via phone 630-447-97SixThree.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>